[MUSIC]
[背景音乐] 翻译: RyukaSuu |审阅: 19waa Coursera Global Translator Community
Okay, so far we've assumed that the only feature relevant to the value of my house,
到目前为止，我们假设与房屋价格相关的唯一特征是
is the square feet of the house.
房子的面积
But I dig into the data set a little bit more, and
但是，当我进一步发掘这些数据
I look at a house that's supposed to be very similar to mine.
我看到另一座房子，与我的房子非常相似
It's a house that has very similar square footage.
它与我屋子面积非常接近
And so, this house is definitely making an influence on what the predictions are for
因此，这座房子必定会对我的房子的预期价格
my house.
有很大的影响
But I look at it and I say, and I look at the specific listing, and
但是当我查看房屋明细时，
it shows that that house only had one bathroom.
它显示那个屋子只有一个卫生间
It's actually quite a big house, only one bathroom.
这房子挺大的 但是只有一个卫生间。
And I say that's really, really not comparable to my house,
我想说 它和我的屋子真是没得比
which has three bathrooms.
我的屋子有三个卫生间呢！
So that the value of that house, that house sales price
因此 那个屋子的价值 也就是它的售价
really shouldn't be indicative of what my house sales price should be.
其实是不能用来作为我的房子的参照的
So instead what we can think about doing is adding more features.
因此 我现在所想做的是 增加更多的特征
So instead of just looking at the relationship between square feet and
而不是仅仅看屋子面积和价格之间的关系
price, we can add number of bathrooms.
我们把卫生间的数量作为特征加入其中
And now for
现在
each one of the listings that I looked at before, I'm gonna have to go through and
对于前面所列出的所有待售房屋 我需要重新查询
record how many square feet that house had, and the number of bathrooms.
并记录每座房子的面积  以及卫生间的数量。
And I'm gonna plot each of these points in the 3D space.
现在我准备将这些点绘制在一个3维空间中
Okay? So it's this hyper cube of square
好 这个立方体就是由
feet versus bathrooms versus price.
房子面积 卫生间数量和价格组成的坐标空间
And now instead of fitting a line to the data, if I'm thinking about just a very
现在我不是用一条直线来拟合这些数据 而是想用一个十分简单的模型
simple model, I can think about fitting a hyper plane.
我能想到的是一个平面
Okay, so it's just a slice through the space.
那么 它只是这个空间的一个切面
We're here.
然后
This is the equation of the hyper plane, and this is the equation of this plane.
我们来看这个平面的方程
So we have w0, which is our intercept, just where this plane lives up and
我们用w0来表示截距 也就是
down on the y-axis.
这个平面在y轴上的位置
And we have w1 times the number of square feet, and
然后我们用w1乘上房屋的面积
w2 times the number of bathrooms.
用w2乘上卫生间的数量
But a question is where do we stop?
但问题是 这样就够了吗？
Do we just want to include the number of bathrooms as our additional feature?
这房子只有卫生间数量 这个额外的特征吗？
There are lots of things we could think about including.
我们还可以加入很多别的特征
We could think about in addition to our square feet, number of bathrooms,
除了有房屋的面积  卫生间的数量
there's the number of bedrooms, the lot size, how old the house is, and
还有卧室的数量 院子的大小 以及房屋的年限
the list goes on and on.
还有很多很多别的特征
In terms of different properties of the house that could be influential in
这些不同的特征都有可能对
assessing it's value.
房屋的售价有影响
But we're gonna actually hold off on this question of looking at which features
那么哪些特征比较重要呢？
are important for this regression task, until we get to the regression course.
我们会等到之后的回归专题课里再去讨论
So go to the regression course to learn more about this topic.
你可以去回归专题课中学习 与此相关的内容
[MUSIC]
[背景音乐] 翻译: RyukaSuu |审阅: 19waa Coursera Global Translator Community